

CONTACT

( 760-532-0531

dryan10101@gmail.com

kadika38.github.io/Portfolio-David-Ryan/

#### **PROFILE**

I am a full stack web developer with experience using JavaScript, CSS, HTML, SQL, React, and MongoDB, among other tools and languages. Always learning a new skill. Detail oriented without losing sight of the big picture. Focused and communicative whether working independently or as part of a team.

#### LINKS

GitHub github.com/Kadika38

Linkedin www.linkedin.com/in/david-ryan-305860183

# DAVID RYAN

### FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

#### **EDUCATION**

UCSD Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Certificate of Completion March - September 2022 A+ Average

Palomar College
Associates in Business
2019-2020
Finance Focus

#### **SKILLS**

**JavaScript** 

CSS

HTML

SQL

React

MongoDB

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Valet Captain @ Ace Parking 2019-Now

Shift Lead role exemplifying customer service in a chaotic environment. Responsible for millions of dollars of vehicles at any given time. Omni Hotel SD 2019-2020 Hard Rock Hotel SD 2020-2022

# DAVID RYAN

## FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

### **CONTACT**

760-532-0531

dryan10101@gmail.com

kadika38.github.io/Portfolio-David-Ryan/

Insert Cover Letter here

David Ryan